As president, I will end once and for all the mass importation of anti-Semitism into the United States.
And just as I did before, we will keep radical Islamic terrorists the hell out of our country.
We're going to keep them out of our country.
We were keeping them out.
You remember the travel ban?
On day one, I will restore our travel ban.
We had a travel ban because we didn't want people coming into our country who really loved the idea of blowing our country up.
Let's blow up our streets and our shopping centers and our people.
So I instituted what we call the Trump travel ban.
And it was an amazing success.
It was suspended immediately upon his coming into the country.
And I never talked.